damage-tagger:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Why are players getting tagged by lava/fall/cactus damage?"
  answer: "You have the `Damage Tagger` expansion installed. Configure it to disable specific non-pvp and non-pve damage causes or delete the expansion."
  related:
    - "delete-expansion"
    - "expansion-configs"

block-commands:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "How do I prevent players from executing commands during combat?"
  answer: "Install the `Cheat Prevention` expansion and open its the `commands.yml` file to modify the commands that are blocked and allowed."
  related:
    - "expansion-configs"
    - "empty-lists"

plugin-yml:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Why do I get a `jar does not contain plugin.yml` error?"
  answer: "Expansions are not plugins. They should be place in the expansions folder."
  related:
    - "expansion-folder"

rewards:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Why am I getting console messages and money when killing mobs?"
  answer: "Configure or remove the Rewards expansion to fix this problem."
  related:
    - "expansion-configs"

potions:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Why are potion effects being removed?"
  answer: "Configure the CheatPrevention expansions potions.yml."
  related:
    - "expansion-configs"

pvp-only:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "How can I make CombatLogX only tag from pvp?"
  answer: "Delete the Mob Tagger and Damage Tagger expansions."
  related:
    - "delete-expansion"

commands:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Why are commands being ran when I enter combat?"
  answer: "You can disable or configure the commands in the commands.yml that's located in the CombatLogX folder. \n **Follow the instructions in the file!!!**"
  related:
    - "empty-lists"

empty-lists:
  question: "How do I make an empty list?"
  answer: "An empty list in yaml looks like this: \n```yaml\nlist-name: []\n```"
  related: []

expansion-configs:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Where is the expansion configs?"
  answer: "You can an expansions configs in `/plugins/CombatLogX/expansions/<expansion name>`."
  related: []

expansion-folder:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Where is the expansions folder?"
  answer: "You can find the expansions folder at `/plugins/CombatLogX/expansions`."
  related:
    - "install-expansion"
    - "delete-expansion"

delete-expansion:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "How do I delete expansions?"
  answer: "Delete the expansion jar and it's folder that's inside the expansion folder and restart."
  related:
    - "expansion-folder"

install-expansion:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "How do I install expansions?"
  answer: "Place the expansion jar in the expansions folder and restart."
  related:
    - "expansion-folder"
    - "find-expansion"
    - "delete-expansion"

find-expansion:
  plugin: "CombatLogX"
  question: "Where can I find expansions?"
  answer: "All official expansions come in the zip file. You can find them in `/CombatLogX/expansions`. "
  related:
    - "expansion-folder"
    - "install-expansion"
    - "delete-expansion"